The Amanda Steele Show.
Today's big up goes to LeBron James' knees.
Okay, in a recent interview, he said that his time in the NBA is winding down.
He's been playing in the NBA for 21 years.
I remember when he was on the cover of ESPN Magazine in 03.
NBA players' knees age like white people in the sun.
So, you know that that meniscus is like, wow, we're about to sit on down.
So the fact that he's playing at such a high level is a testament to whatever bionic cartilage
he does have going on in those knees.
Let down.
Goes to whoever is assigned to write Donald Trump's I Have a Dream speech.
Stephen Miller, a former White House advisor and known white nationalist,
is reportedly involved in a plan to take legal actions aimed at reinterpreting civil rights laws
to focus on anti-white racism.
You heard that right.
So you know that at some point then, if Trump gets elected,
he is going to have to make his I Have a Dream speech.
Which means there will be a white civil rights movement coming.
Like, that's what we're doing.
And it's going to be called a white civil rights movement when it is actually a Klan rally.
They will say, just sit in at the local Starbucks.
They'll demand fair treatment for white people in the pumpkin spice latte line.
So as we continue to figure out, oh my gosh, like what bullet are we going to bite in this election?
Just know that that is a prime directive of Trump's cabinet and his administration.
They are going to focus on anti-white racism, which by the way, does not exist.
So we're clear.
We are, we are, we are.